I'm in Bangkok today and fun fact Hiro Gato who's making beautiful spandex
catsuits has its headquarter here so of course I'm taking the chance and have a
look around and you're coming with me. To be dressed appropriately I bought my own
Hiro Gato suit from home on holiday and I'm going to change into that now.
Alright, let's go!
It's getting dark too soon
A threatening silence surrounding me
A wind comes up from the islands
When distance fades to stormy grey
Watch out from the deep of the ocean here. I will stand to face your
The centerpiece of every Hirogato piece is the cat ear and I have the honor to press
as a cat on a piece now.
I'm standing here in front of the sample collection.
There are various products and especially all the fabrics.
I'm going to show you a few of them because they're so cool.
A classic rainbow PU.
Always good for everything.
Okay, I've never even seen this before.
It's super trippy with all the mushrooms.
And it's sparkly.
Really, really cool.
iClassic spandex fabric with a pattern and this one is a coated spandex bodysuit.
I think the light is awesome on this one.
the lifetime
No rain can wash away
my tears
No wind can soothe my pain
You made me doubt
You made me fear
But now I'm not the same
You took my wife
My hand on
So I will turn into
the deep of the ocean
I don't pretend
that I love you
because there is nothing left to lose
the love in you
Hi, I'm sitting here with Stefan and actually we could talk German with each other because you're from Germany
I am
Yeah, and I am too, so let's switch to English again
Alright
How did you come up with moving to Thailand and starting this company?
I'm a lawyer, I studied law in Germany, back in Germany and then I came here to do my Master of Law
and then I never left.
Okay, how long is that ago?
17 years.
Wow, okay. And you started Hirokato and I learned that I'm not pronouncing it correctly, so how would you pronounce it?
So you speak Thai? Yeah, I do.
That's so crazy actually that I'm here in Bangkok speaking with a person from Germany who founded this company.
I'm very happy you came. Thanks for having me.
How many pieces do you produce per month roughly?
It depends. This month is like Christmas season. It's like 500 to 600 pieces.
Wow, okay. And usually we are at about 300 to 400 pieces.
And you built your own production upstairs. I've visited it. It's really impressive.
I did, yeah. You started the company from scratch. How did you come up with the idea?
So I started with t-shirts, but I always wanted to do some spandex stuff.
But I didn't want to go too far to the fetish side.
I wanted to have a presentation which would be more on the fashion end.
And make Spendex fashionable. That was the idea.
The first name was going to be Hiro.
And then Cat is Gato in Spanish.
So it's Hiro the Cat.
Hiro the Cat. So Hiro is the name basically. There's no translation?
There is no translation. It's the first name in Japan.
And the cat, of course. I love the cat by the way.
I think it's really part of the outfit. I wouldn't change it.
What's planned for the future? Are there any new products coming? Anything special?
Yes, I am excited to let you know that we are planning to do sportswear.
I got some samples with me if you want to take a look.
these are like the leggings i love the red cats that's cool that's what i can and here's one more
design glitter oh i think you can see the pattern which is cool like nylon spandex and this did we
yes so nice oh there's ah okay nice looking forward to that i sent you something yeah thank
you and if you want to buy some HiroGasio check out my affiliate code in the
description text and also link to the webshop I of course put everything down
there leave us a comment and give us a like and thank you for having me today
it was really fun and I hope I will see you in the next video I hope I see you
again sometime in the future when I'm going to come back in Germany
Alright, bye.
Thank you.